(Leonard:)Fine. Assuming
that everything you say is true...
(Leonard:)...how does the biologically superior
Homo novus get to work...
(Leonard:)...tomorrow morning?
(Sheldon:)Homo novus doesn't know.
(Leonard:)Well, hang in there.
(Leonard:)Maybe you'll evolve into something
with wings.
SHELDON: Good morning, gentlemen.
- Hey.
(Sheldon:)Good morning.
(Raj:)Is there some new kind of Casual Friday
I don't know about?
(Leonard:)No, he lives here now.
(Howard:)Really? Why?
(Leonard:)Well, since he won't take the bus
and he's too evolved to drive...
...he decided to sleep in his office...
(Leonard:)...and shower in the radiation lab
until I'm finished with my experiment.
(Raj:)But you finished your experiment
a week ago.
(Leonard:)Yep.
[IN SPANISH]
[LOUD BANGING]
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
(Sheldon:)You saw nothing.